pelfusion.com 2012-06-02

# Privacy Policy | PelFusion

[Home](http://pelfusion.com/)  »  Privacy Policy

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

## Cookies And Web Beacons

PelFusion.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Website content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends through browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

\- Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads on PelFusion.com

\- Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to PelFusion.com and other sites on the Internet.

\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. 

## Privacy Contact

If you need any information or have any questions about our privacy policy, you can contact us by email at info[at]pelfusion[dot]com.
